tradebit.com 2012-12-29

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy policy to protect you and us!**

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This policy covers how TRADEBIT treats personal information that TRADEBIT collects and receives, including information related to your past use of TRADEBIT products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that TRADEBIT does not own or control, or to people that TRADEBIT does not employ or manage. 

* * *

**Information Collection and Use**

* * *

**General**

  * TRADEBIT collects personal information when you register with TRADEBIT, when you visit TRADEBIT pages or the pages of certain TRADEBIT partners. TRADEBIT may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 
  * When you register we may ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some services we may also ask for your address, Social Security number, and other personal information. Once you register with TRADEBIT and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * TRADEBIT collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer. 
  * TRADEBIT automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, TRADEBIT cookie information, and the page you request. 
  * TRADEBIT uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

* * *

**Children**

  * TRADEBIT does not allow a child under age 13 to register with our services. 

* * *

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * TRADEBIT does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with TRADEBIT under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help TRADEBIT communicate with you about offers from TRADEBIT and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of TRADEBIT's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if TRADEBIT is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, TRADEBIT will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  * TRADEBIT displays targeted advertisements based on personal information.

  * TRADEBIT does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 
  * TRADEBIT advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 
  * TRADEBIT works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. 

**Cookies**

  * TRADEBIT may set and access TRADEBIT cookies on your computer. 

* * *

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

**General**  

  * You can edit your TRADEBIT Account Information at any time. 
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the TRADEBIT service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the TRADEBIT Newsletter, that are considered part of your TRADEBIT account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 
  * You can delete your TRADEBIT account by visiting the **Account Deletion** page in the member area for the free accounts or just cancel your subscription with PayPal or 2checkout. 

* * *

**Confidentiality and Security**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * ev1servers.net, our hosting company, has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 

* * *

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * TRADEBIT may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your TRADEBIT account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

* * *

**Questions and Suggestions**

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please send us an e-mail to **info @ tradebit.com** or you can contact us at: 

Tradebit, Inc.  
Customer Care - Privacy Policy Issues  
3422 Old Capital Trail  
Suite 717  
19808 Wilmington, DE  
USA  
Fax: +1-480-275-3582  

Effective Date: June 20th, 2006
